1. SQUAT / ANTERIOR (1 MINUTE PER EXERCISE / REST-PAUSE IF NEEDED)
Alt. Single Leg Box Squats (use low box if advanced / higher box for beginners)
1 1/2 Bottomed Out Squats (to failure)
Jump Squats

2. UPPER PUSH (1 MINUTE PER EXERCISE / REST-PAUSE IF NEEDED)
Handstand Pushups OR Power Pushaways
Rotational Pushups OR Knee Rotational Pushups
Cobra Pushups (long head contracted) OR Knee Cobra Pushups

3. HINGE / POSTERIOR (1 MINUTE PER EXERCISE / REST-PAUSE IF NEEDED)
Alt. Single Leg Heel Touch Squats (use “kickstand” if needed)
Alt. Sprinter Lunges 
Plyo Sprinter Lunges (jump from higher position if more beginner)

4. UPPER PULL (1 MINUTE PER EXERCISE / REST-PAUSE IF NEEDED)
Pullups OR Seated Pullups
Human Pullovers OR BW Sliding Pulldowns
Inverted Chin Curls

5. ABS (1 MINUTE PER EXERCISE / REST-PAUSE IF NEEDED)
Reverse Corkscrews
Black Widow Knee Slides
Levitation Crunches

6. CORRECTIVE (1 MINUTE PER EXERCISE / REST-PAUSE IF NEEDED)
Angels and Devils

COMPLETE 1-2 MORE ROUNDS (TOTAL WORKOUT TIME: 35-50 MINUTES)

Here is how to construct the perfect home workout B:

HINGE / POSTERIOR x 3 ROUNDS
Slick Floor Bridge Curl (Single Leg) OR Slick Floor Bridge Curl (Dual Leg)
Long Leg March
High Hip Bucks

LUNGE / ANTERIOR x 3 ROUNDS
Alt. Crossover Step Ups
Alt. Reverse Lunges
Split Squat Jumps

UPPER PUSH x 3 ROUNDS
Variable Wall Pushups OR Knee Decline Pushups to Knee Flat Pushups
Alt. BW Side Lateral Raises (from knees for beginners)
Tricep BW Extensions (long head stretch)

UPPER PULL x 3 ROUNDS
Chin Ups OR Seated Chin Ups
Inverted Rows
Back Widows

ABS x 2 ROUNDS
Ab Halos
V-Up Tucks
Sit-Up Elbow Thrusts

CORRECTIVE x 2 ROUNDS
Reverse Hypers

COMPLETE 1-2 MORE ROUNDS (TOTAL WORKOUT TIME: 35-50 MINUTES)
